What?
（福井(ふくい)）はあ？
Hey, what'd you just say?
（福井）
ちょ… おい 今 何つった？
I told you. I've had enough.
（紫原(むらさきばら)）
だ〜から〜 もういいや
I quit. Sub me out.
オレ やーめた！
交代してよ
Don't be ridiculous!
（福井）ふざけんな こら！
What are you talking about?!
いきなり 何考えてんだ テメエ！
No one can stop Kagami anymore.
Translation Checking: AMS
だってもう 誰も火神(かがみ)
止めらんないじゃん
（氷室(ひむろ)）ううっ！
（紫原）うっ！
You have what I desperately want,
（氷室）オレが
喉から手が出るほど—
欲してるものを
持ってる オマエが—
and you're trying to throw the game.
あっさり勝負を
投げようとしている
You're making me crazy with rage. Absolutely crazy.
（氷室）
怒りで気がヘンになるぜ
いいかげん…
Editing: AMS
Get away from me. That's so annoying.
うわあ 引くわ…
そういうの 心底ウザい
Timing: sangofe
K-Timing: Eternal Blizzard
Typesetting: AMS, KmE
Anyway, I can't believe you're crying.
てか あり得ないわ 泣くとか
I sort of noticed, but I didn't know you felt this strongly.
何となく気付いてはいたけど—
ここまでとは思ってなかったよ
Actually, this is the first time I've been amazed
つうか 初めてだよ
ウザすぎて—
by how much someone's repulsed me.
逆にすげえと思うのは
Karaoke: KmE
（日向(ひゅうが)）何かモメてたけど
大丈夫か？
They were fighting about something.
Is everything okay?
No, it's probably the opposite.
（火神）
いや… むしろ逆じゃないスか
Encoding: Your Mom
They're more dangerous than ever.
（黒子(くろこ)）今までで一番—
ヤバそうです
This does look bad.
（伊月(いづき)）確かにヤバそうだな
And so do we, in a different way.
（日向）違う意味で… こっちもな
ゾーンは消耗もハンパない
Being in the Zone is exhausting.
Will he last until the end?
最後まで持つか…？
I was watching you during the time out.
タイムアウト中
見てましたけど—
正直 諦めたんじゃないかと
思ってました
Honestly, I thought you'd given up.
Yeah. I tried to, but I changed my mind.
そうしようと思ったけど
やめた
I'll crush you after all.
やっぱ ひねり潰すわ
めんどくさくなりそうで
嫌だけど—
It might be annoyingly difficult,
but I hate losing even more.
負けるのは もっと嫌なの
saizen-fansubs.com
Good.
よかった…
But I hate losing too.
けど—
負けるの嫌なのは
ボクも同じですから！
Kuroko's
I
(
)
I
(
)
Basketball
Episode
Win!
Murasakibara's not the only one.
（伊月）紫原だけじゃない…
Looks like Himuro's had a breakthrough too.
氷室も何かふっきれた感じだ…
A screen!
（伊月）スクリーン！
（岡村(おかむら)）ううっ！
It's no use.
（福井）ダメだ…
ミラージュシュートは—
The Mirage Shot's been completely beaten.
完全に攻略された！
I hate to admit it,
（氷室）悔しいが…
（火神）うん？
but you truly are amazing, Taiga.
認めるよ
やっぱり オマエはすごいよ…
タイガ
I've lost our battle.
約束の勝負はもう…
オレの負けでいい
だが 悪いな
Sorry, though.
We're still going to win!
それでも勝つのは オレたちだ
（紫原）ぐうっ！
なっ！ パスだと！？
A pass?
（岡村）あっ 何！？
What?
（荒木）常軌を逸している…
This isn't normal.
Is he really this good?
これほどか…！
（紫原）言ったろ
I told you already. I hate losing.
負けんのは嫌なんだよ
That's why I'll win!
だから勝つ！
フンッ！
（さつき）ウソ…
You're kidding.
Whoa, I've never seen Murasakibara like this before.
（青峰(あおみね)）へえ…
初めてだぜ あんな紫原は
（黄瀬(きせ)）
アハハ… マジっスか…
Seriously?
（選手たち）うおしゃあ！
All right!
This is really looking bad.
ちょっと ヤバすぎだろ
（火神）伊月先輩
ちょっといいスか？
Izuki, do you have a minute?
（劉(リュウ)･岡村）な！？
今度は オマエが
ポイントガードかよ！
You're the point guard now?
（火神）うっ… おらっ！
（伊月）フンッ！
皮肉なもんだな
It's ironic.
チームプレイが信条の誠凛(せいりん)が—
The team-oriented Seirin is relying solely on Kagami on offense.
火神頼みの攻め
And Murasakibara's Yosen is playing together on offense.
紫原のいる陽泉(ようせん)が—
連係での攻めとはよ…
だが—
However, without a defensive trump card on either team,
両チームともディフェンスに
決め手がない以上—
ここからは 取りこぼせば命取りだ
missed shots will be fatal.
（リコ）河原(かわはら)君
（河原）あっ
Kawahara!
（火神）うりゃっ！
（紫原）フンッ！
Seirin
Yosen
No one's giving any ground!
Seirin
Yosen
（観客１）
おおっ！ どっちも譲らねえ
Yosen
Seirin
（観客２）残り１分
勝つのはどっちだっ！？
Who's going to win in the last minute?
Yosen
Seirin
Damn it.
（伊月）くそっ…
ついていくのに精一杯だ
Just keeping up takes everything we have.
In order to close the gap, we have to stop their teamwork.
（日向）点差を縮めるには—
どこかで あの連係を
止めなきゃなんねえのに
火神だって
すでにギリギリもいいとこだ
Kagami's already nearing his limit.
どうする…
What should we do?
We're one step short of winning the game.
勝つためには
あと一歩足りない！
White ball!
（審判）白ボール
（アナウンス）
黒 メンバーチェンジです
Black, member change!
Why's everyone so gloomy?
（木吉(きよし)）
何だ 何だ みんな暗いぞ？
We're nearly there.
あと一歩じゃねえか
楽しんでこうぜ！
Let's go have some fun.
あぁ… おかえりなさい
Welcome back.
（木吉）ただいま
I'm home.
（日向）木吉！
Kiyoshi!
（リコ）
ラスト１分… 行ってこい！
It's the final minute.
Go get 'em!
（荒木）何やら裏で
やっているとは思っていたが—
I knew they were up to something.
They've been helping him recover his strength.
体力回復に努めていたか…
マジかよ！
Seriously?
まさか戻ってくるとはのう
I didn't think he'd come back.
Atsushi destroyed him mentally and physically.
（氷室）心身ともに敦(あつし)に
打ちのめされてなお…
“鉄心”の名は だてじゃないか…
They don't call him the Iron Heart for nothing.
I'm sick of this.
（紫原）ったく… あきれるよ
何回 ひねり潰されれば
気が済むの？
How many times do you need to be crushed?
You're way too tough.
しぶとすぎでしょ
That's my strength.
それが売りだからな
つうか
状況分かってんだろな 木吉
You know what's going on, don't you, Kiyoshi?
You kept us waiting long enough.
ギリギリも いいとこだぞ
I know.
（木吉）分かってるさ！
We're just in a pinch, right?
ただのピンチだろ？
The game isn't over.
終わったわけじゃない
楽しんでこうぜ！
Let's go have some fun!
It's the moment of truth.
（笠松(かさまつ)）
さあ ここからが正念場だ！
残り50秒切って ４点差…
They're four points behind with less than 50 seconds remaining.
誠凛が勝つためには—
If Seirin lets them score any more, it's over.
これ以上 点をやったら終わりだ
つまり—
In other words, they have to repeatedly stop Yosen
ここから陽泉の攻撃を
連続で止め—
while repeatedly making their own shots.
連続で決めなきゃならねえ
果たして この超難関…
Can Seirin overcome such a difficult obstacle?
突破できるか 誠凛…
It's a triangle-and-two defense.
（福井）これは—
トライアングルツー！
With Kiyoshi back, they reverted to the defense they ran in the first half.
木吉が戻ってきたことで—
前半と同じ型に 戻してきたか！
They're being careful.
さすがに慎重だね
Yeah, but they've made up their minds.
…が
ハラは決まったみてえだな
来るぜ
Here it comes.
（氷室）フンッ
（紫原）ううっ… フンッ！
（火神）おら！
He's as amazing as ever.
（福井）相変わらず すげえ…
But there's one more pass here.
…が ここからもう一度—
リターンがあるんだよ！
（紫原）えいっ！ あっ！
Kiyoshi?
（福井）木吉！？
（氷室）悪いが…
Sorry, but only Kagami can stop me.
火神でなければ止められないよ
（小金井）ミラージュシュート！
The Mirage Shot!
（土田(つちだ)）ダメだ…
It's no use!
木吉にあれは 止められない！
Kiyoshi can't stop it!
No, it's not over yet!
いいえ まだよ！
２回リリースする—
In order to stop the double release of the Mirage Shot,
ミラージュシュートを
止めるには—
you don't have to be able to block both shots like Kagami.
火神君のように
両方 防ぐほかに もう１つ…
You can predict when he's going to release.
どちらで打つか
読み切ればいいのよ
For Teppei, with his Right of Postponement,
後出しの権利を持つ
鉄平(てっぺい)にとって—
that's his forte!
それは十八番(おはこ)よ！
（降旗(ふりはた)）うわっ １度目の
リリースのタイミングで跳んだ！？
He jumped on the first release?
That's his decision.
（氷室）そうきたか…
だが 分かっているよ
But I know...
It's a fake.
それはフェイクだろう？
Fooling your teammates with a fake is impressive.
（氷室）味方もかかるほどの
フェイクは大したものだ
普通なら
まず反応してしまうだろう
A normal person would have fallen for it.
However, that's my specialty.
だが—
その分野は オレの専売特許
Fakes don't work against me!
オレにフェイクは通じない！
He predicted his move.
（福井）読み勝った！
このまま
１度目のリリースで打てば—
If he shoots on the first release, he won't make it in time!
間に合わねえ！
（岡村）これで終わりじゃ！
It's over!
I knew I couldn't win a battle of prediction.
分かってたよ
読み勝てないことは
だから負けることにした
That's why I chose to lose
２度目を止めようとして
失敗するほうで
by trying and failing to stop it on the second release.
ミラージュシュートは
その性質上—
Due to the nature of the Mirage Shot,
一度目のリリースは
最高点に達する前にする必要がある
the first release must be made before you reach the apex of your jump.
In other words, because the first release has a lower release point,
つまり—
リリースポイントが低い
１度目に限れば—
高さが劣る選手でも届くのさ！
it can even be stopped by shorter players!
（日向）ふんがっっ！
It's time to pick up the pace
dondon ikimashou
All right!
（部員たち）よおっしゃあー！
before I lose out to some go-getter,
tsuyoki de semeraretanda
nakamauchi no warai banashi de wa
and end up like the guys my friends joke about.
Stop them!
（荒木）止めろ！
ここは絶対 取らせるな！
Don't let them score!
It's starting to drive me crazy...
monmon toshitenda ze
Always cooped up in my room.
jibun no heya itsu datte
The truth is, I've got a timid peach mind
honto wa yowaki na peach mind
Does she have a thing for me?
ki no aru soburi ka
Or am I reading too much into it?
tada no omoikomi ka
Rebound!
（部員たち）リバウンド！
Either way, that girl's got us all figured out.
baretenda ano ko ni wa
Do your best, boys.
ganbare otoko no ko
If this keeps up, it'll be 35 straight losses.
kono mama ja sanjuugo renpai
But just for you, I'll be your go-to guy.
kimi dake no boku wa Go to guy
Phantasmagoric magical star
hengenjizai no majikaru sutaa
What's wrong with a tried-and-true stereotype?
idai naru manneri datte ii ja nai
Own up to your own inexperience.
itomero aosa wo
If your love has yet to come full circle,
mada michinu koi naraba
Yosen
Seirin
I'll give you my all.
zenbu ageru ze
Yosen
Seirin
Twenty seconds remaining!
（小金井）残り20秒！
Yosen
Seirin
We're finally one point behind!
Yosen
Seirin
（土田）ついに１点差だ！
Yosen
Seirin
This I swear to you.
kimi ni chikau
Yosen
Seirin
Amazing.
すごい…
If they make one more basket, it'll be a comeback.
これで もう１ゴール
決めれば逆転！？
Yeah.
If they make the shot.
決められればな
Kuroko's
I
Basketball
Seirin
Go! We need one more basket!
当たれ！
もう一本取るんだ！
Let's beat Yosen!
勝つぞ 陽泉に！
Honestly, I'm on my last legs.
（福井）正真正銘—
最後の力を 振り絞って来てる
We can't even throw the ball in freely.
（劉）スローインすら
ままならないアル！
Give me the ball!
よこせ 劉！
The sting of defeat and the joy of victory.
ka
mi
shi
me
ta
n
da
hai
bo
ku
mo
tsu
ka
n
da
sho
u
ri
mo
Why do I keep pushing forward? I can't say for sure yet.
na
n
no
ta
me
ni
ga
n
ba
ru
no
ma
da
mi
e
nai
ke
do
勝つ…！ とどめさしてやる！
I'll win!
I'll finish this game!
But we'll still fight our way through. I know we will.
so
re
de
mo
i
ku
n
da
rou
so
re
da
ke
wa
shi
tte
i
ru
Social standing and reputation be damned.
chi
i
ya
me
i
you
da
ke
na
n
ka
ja
nai
ze
Kagami?
（福井）火神！？
（岡村）バケモノめ…！
That monster!
Go. Don't worry about passing anymore.
行け もうパスはいい
We just need to keep looking forward.
mu
ka
u
sa
ki
wa
ma
e
da
ke
de
i
ここで決めるのが—
It's your job to make this shot.
オマエの仕事だ
All you'll get looking down is a view of the ground.
shi
ta
wo
mu
i
ta
tte
ji
me
n
shi
ka
mi
e
na
i
So let's go as far as we can go!
da
ka
ra
i
ke
ru
to
ko
ma
de
What's going on?
どうなってる これは…
Let
me
high
er!
Get
me
high
er!
This power...
このパワーは…
His dunk is even stronger than before!
今までの
どのダンクよりも強(つえ)え…
The fire inside me is burning bright.
mo
e
ru
mi
no
a
tsu
sa
wa
This isn't good.
こいつ ヤベエ…
Even on this day like any other
na
n
to
na
ku
no
kyo
u
de
mo
He's going to push through me.
このままじゃ—
押し切られ… うぅ… あっ
we're burnin' up, love, and believe.
burn
in'
up,
we
love
shi
n
ji
te
Rock
me,
ba
by.
Show
me,
ba
by.
Don't give up.
（木吉）諦めるな
Let's see more of what we can do.
mi
se
te
ku
re
mo
tto
We're winning this game!
勝つぞ… 必ず！
Don't live in your dreams. You don't need to tell me.
yu
me
ni
i
ki
ru
na
i
tte
ku
re
ru
na
Kiyoshi!
（日向）木吉！
戻ってたのか？
He's made it back!
The way you and I are gonna create
o
re
to
ki
mi
to
de
tsu
ku
ri
a
ge
ru
n
da
our legendary other selves.
de
n
se
tsu
wo
o
ther
self
（３人）やったぁー！
All right!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
Counterattack!
カウンター！
（日向）ちょっと待て
Hold on.
なぜ もう そんなところに…
How is he there already?
いくら何でも速すぎる！
He got there way too quickly.
（火神）まさか…
Could it be?
Murasakibaracchi...
（黄瀬）紫原っち…！
He's in.
（青峰）入りやがった…
（黄瀬）ダメだ…
This isn't good.
If they're both in the Zone, Kagamicchi can't win.
お互いゾーンに入った状態なら—
火神っちに勝ち目はない！
And he's already at his limit.
（青峰）しかも とっくに
限界もいいとこだ
Things are looking hopeless.
いよいよ絶望的だぜ
（一同）火神！
Kagami!
Not yet!
（火神）まだだ…
Give me every last drop!
絞り出せ！
最後の一滴まで…
We'll win!
オレたちは勝つ！
It's the ace's job to carry everyone's hopes to victory!
（火神）みんなの想いを背負って
決めんのがエースだ！
限界なんて
いくらでも超えてやる！
I'll exceed my limits as much as I need to!
（岡村）レーンアップ！？
（雅子･劉）あっ
A lane up?!
This doesn't look right.
（氷室）いや… だが おかしい！
He couldn't make it from this angle earlier in the game.
この角度では
前への飛距離が足りてない…
He doesn't have enough room to get to the hoop.
これではリングに届かない！
（アレックス）
まさか やる気か あれを…
Is he trying to do that now?
だが ゾーンに入っている
今ならできるかもしれない
But now that he's in the Zone, he may be able to pull it off.
ミラージュシュートを
静の技とするなら—
If the Mirage Shot is a technique of stillness,
豪の技とでも呼ぶべき
無敵のシュート
that unstoppable shot is one of intense power.
流星のダンク… メテオジャム！
The falling star dunk:
Meteor Jam!
（氷室）あっ…
（岡村･木吉）うわぁ
All right!
（部員たち）やったー！
（土田）逆転… 逆転だ！
A comeback!
Yosen
Seirin
We've taken the lead!
Yosen
Seirin
ハァ…
（紫原）くっ…
（木吉）あっ… まだだ！
It's not over yet!
Atsushi!
（氷室）敦！
（福田(ふくだ)）ああっ！
（降旗）カウンター！
A counterattack!
Kagami!
火神！？
（氷室）跳べない！？ そんな…
He can't jump? Impossible.
After Kiyoshi became the point guard,
木吉ポイントガード以降
敦は あの巨体で—
Atsushi was made to jump over and over again with his giant body.
今までにないほど
連続の跳躍をしてきた
その負荷に—
His knees couldn't handle the burden.
ヒザが耐えきれなく
なっていたのか…！
（紫原）ふざけんな！
Don't be ridiculous.
The hoop's right there.
ゴールは すぐそこだ
Even if I can't jump, I can just toss it in!
跳べなくても放ればいいだけ…
It wasn't their intention.
（黒子）決して
意図していたわけではありません
kasunda mirai wo kirisaku you ni terasu hikari
Like a shining light that cuts through the hazy future,
Nevertheless, this is still the result of Kiyoshi and the upperclassmen's tenacity.
それでも これは—
木吉先輩たちの 執念の結果です
musuu no kanousei wo motome
I chase after unlimited possibilities.
And that's why, with this,
だから これで—
Gotta open my eyes
終わりだ！
it ends!
Wake up sabitsuita me ni hi wo tomose
Wake up, light a fire in your tired eyes.
Yosen
Get up kusubutteru baai ja nainda zettai
Get up! Now's definitely not the time to let it smoulder.
youi sareta risou nante iranai
You don't need to have some big dream.
yuragu koto no nai ishi to
Just an unwavering spirit,
mikansei na chizu de ii kara
and an unfinished map is enough.
Kurokocchi knew Murasakibaracchi couldn't jump.
（黄瀬）黒子っちは気付いてた
asu wo tsukame kono te de
Hold on to tomorrow with these hands!
紫原っちが跳べないことを
けど 決して確証はなかったし—
detarame na rizumu de nurikaete iku kako ni
Regretting a past that's being overwritten by a nonsensical rhythm...
However, he had no conclusive evidence,
and the possibility was remote.
可能性は低かった
koukai hitotsu arienai daro
That's not possible, right?
それでも なお—
Yet he unhesitatingly went straight for the block.
一歩も迷いなくブロックに向かった
ari no mama no biito de kurikaeshite iku genzei wo
I'll rewrite things with the true beat now,
（黄瀬）諦めるってことを
知らなすぎっスよ… ホント
He really just never gives up.
kasaneta mirai kagayaku you ni
and create a sparkling future.
（審判）73対72で—
With a score of 73 to 72, Seirin High wins!
kizami konda sonzai wo kesshou toshite
Your existence is etched as a crystal.
誠凛高校の勝ち！—
Bow!
礼！
Thank you very much!
（選手たち）
ありがとうございました！
Keep it in my story
（岡村）負けたわい
We lost.
あざっした
Thanks.
負けたよ タイガ…
I lost, Taiga.
As per our promise, I won't call myself your brother anymore.
約束通り もうオレは
兄とは名乗らない
Yeah, I know.
ああ… 分かったよ
（木吉）紫原
Murasakibara.
またやろうな
Let's play again sometime.
What?
No way.
ヤだよ…
だって—
I'm
オレもう バスケやめるし
quitting basketball.
I played until the end because Muro-chin was so desperate,
室(むろ)ちんが
あんまり必死だったから—
最後までやったけど—
but it wasn't fun.
やっぱ つまんなかったし—
ただでさえ
面白くないスポーツなのに—
It's already a boring enough sport.
負けちゃったら
これ以上やる意味なんてねえよ
There's no reason to keep playing after I've lost.
そっか
I see.
じゃあ しょうがないな
I guess it can't be helped then.
If that's how you really feel.
もし それが
オマエの本音だったらな
Is he really going to quit?
やめちまうのか アイツ…
No way.
まさか
だって彼が—
After all, he doesn't truly hate basketball.
心底バスケを
嫌いなはずありませんから
We'll win next time, Atsushi.
（氷室）次は勝とうな 敦！
What?
いや だから…
I told you,
I'm quitting.
やめるって言ってんじゃん…
そうか
You sure?
It doesn't look that way to me.
けど オレには
そうは見えないけどな
オマエは まだこれからじゃ！
頑張れ！
You're just getting started.
Keep at it.
You did well, guys.
（荒木）全員よくやった！
Let's go home.
帰るぞ！
Yeah!
（陽泉部員たち）うす！
In order to enter the Zone, you must love basketball.
ゾーンに入るのに必要な
バスケを好きな気持ち…
ムッ君には
ずっとなかったはずでしょ？
I thought Muk never felt that way.
まあな
I guess.
He entered the Zone though.
けど アイツは入った
つまりは そういうことだろ
That can only mean one thing.
Good work, guys.
みんな お疲れ！
We can celebrate later.
喜ぶのは
ひとまず あとにして—
次が待ってるから 出るわよ！
The next teams are waiting.
Let's go.
その試合で勝ったほうが
明日の相手だ
Whoever wins that game will be our opponent tomorrow.
このまま 上 上がるぞ！
Let's head upstairs.
Yes, sir!
（部員たち）はい
（日向）次は… 準決勝だ
The semifinals are next!
I've got the urge to challenge these bold-faced lies.
shoudou ga atte usoppachi ni idonde
You and I are the stars of this love song.
boku to kimi to ga shujinkou Love song
It's time to pick up the pace
dondon ikimashou
before I lose out to some go-getter,
tsuyoki de semeraretanda
and end up like the guys my friends joke about.
nakamauchi no warai banashi de wa
It's starting to drive me crazy...
monmon toshitenda ze
セミファイナルで
待ってます
We're waiting for you in the semifinals.
Always cooped up in my room.
jibun no heya itsu datte
See you soon.
モチロンっスよ
The truth is, I've got a timid peach mind.
honto wa yowaki na peach mind
Does she have a thing for me?
ki no aru soburi ka
Or am I reading too much into it?
tada no omoikomi ka
Either way, that girl's got us all figured out.
baretenda ano ko ni wa
Do your best, boys.
ganbare otoko no ko
If this keeps up, it'll be 35 straight losses.
kono mama ja sanjuugo renpai
But just for you, I'll be your go-to guy.
kimi dake no boku wa Go to guy
Phantasmagoric magical star
hengenjizai no majikaru sutaa
What's wrong with a tried-and-true stereotype?
idai naru manneri datte ii ja nai
Own up to your own inexperience.
itomero aosa wo
If your love has yet to come full circle,
mada michinu koi naraba
I'll give you my all.
zenbu ageru ze
This I swear to you.
kimi ni chikau
Kagami, do you have a minute?
（黒子）火神君
ちょっといいですか？
What?
I'm
ボク 今—
ムカついてるんですけど
really mad right now.
Why?!
（火神）なんで！？
What are you talking about?
何 言ってんだ
試合勝ったじゃねーか！
We won the game.
（黒子）問題は そのあとです
The problem is what happened after that.
Are you happy with what happened with Himuro?
氷室さんと…
あれで よかったんですか？
I can't help that.
しょうがねえだろ！
Win or lose, we're not brothers anymore.
勝っても負けても兄弟やめる
そういう約束だったんだからよ
That's the promise we made.
What are you two, idiots?
（黒子）
そろいもそろって アホですか
What?!
I told you to throw that out!
オマッ… これ捨てろって…
I couldn't throw it away.
捨てるわけないでしょう
If anything,
というか むしろ—
ボクには あのとき
“捨てないでくれ”—
it sounded to me like you were asking me not to.
と言ってるようにしか
聞こえませんでしたが？
Close game, Tatsuya.
（アレックス）
惜しかったな タツヤ
Yes.
But I feel refreshed now.
けど 今はスッキリしてるよ
Sorry, Alex.
すまない アレックス
オレは あのとき…
I was...
Don't worry about it.
気にするな
Athletes get worked up before a game all the time.
試合前に 選手が
気が立ってるなんて—
よくあることだろ
Anyway, it was a good game.
それより…
いいゲームだったよ
わざわざ 日本まで
見にきたかいがあった
It was worth the trip here to Japan.
アレックス
Alex...
I won't deny how you felt then.
（黒子）あのときの火神君を—
否定するつもりはありません
けど—
But
is it really so difficult to continue
兄弟であることと
ライバルであること
その両方で
ありつづけることは—
being brothers and rivals?
そんな難しいことですか？
Thanks, Kuroko!
悪(わり)い 黒子！
Win!